Finding Aid for Donald W. Riegle, Jr. papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Senatorial Papers, 1977-1994
  - Legislative, 1977-1994
    - 96th Congress, 1977-1978
      - Nutrition Labeling and Information amendments (S.1651 S.1652)
        - 1979 (Box 31)
        - Hearings, March 1980 (Box 31)
      - Senate Democratic task force on the economy (Box 31)
      - Sleeping Bear Dunes National Lakeshore (Box 31)
      - Special projects, 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Sunset Act (S.2) -- Labor Committee file (Box 31)
    - 97th Congress, 1981-1982
      - Alcohol and drug abuse services (Box 31)
      - Auto summit (Box 31)
      - Business loan program (S.2956) -- McLouth Steel Company, 3 folders (Box 31)
      - Chrysler loan guarantee (Box 31)
      - Board report -- final resolutions
        - Final resolutions (folder 1) (Box 31)
        - Final resolutions (folder 1) (Box 32)
      - Community Schools and Comprehensive Community Education Act (S.2711) (Box 32)
      - Comprehensive Alcoholism Act amendments (S.755)
        - Block grant hearing (Box 32)
        - Hearings (Box 32)
        - House bill (Box 32)
        - Humphrey amendment (Box 32)
        - Riegle amendments (Box 32)
      - Davis-Bacon Act (Box 32)
      - Disability amendments (Box 32)
      - Education -- Pell grant (Box 32)
      - Equal Rights Amendment (Box 32)
      - Federal Unemployment Tax Act amendments (S.2047) (Box 32)
      - Foreign affairs
        - Ireland (Box 32)
        - Romania (Box 32)
      - General Services Administration services purchase of foreign trucks (Box 32)
      - Health Care for Unemployed Workers Act (S.1154) (Box 32)
      - Immigration Reform and Control Act (Box 32)
      - Japanese internment and relocation during World War II (Box 32)
      - Legal Services Corporation
        - Board members (Box 32)
        - Class action (Box 32)
        - Michigan (Box 32)
      - Louis, Joe (S.1079) (Box 32)
      - Michigan -- Memos from staff (Box 32)
      - Mid-East peace plan (Box 32)
      - National Commission on Neurofibromatosis Act (S.2901) (Box 32)
      - Parental Kidnapping Prevention Act (S.1759) (Box 32)
      - Pictured Rocks National Lakeshore (S.620) (Box 32)
      - Regulatory Reform Amendment (S.1080) (Box 32)
      - Riegle statements (Box 32)
      - Social Security Amendments (S1669) (Box 32)
      - Budget Committee file (Box 32)
      - Labor Committee file -- Statements and press (Box 32)
      - Hospice coverage (Box 32)
      - Sleeping Bear Dunes National Lakeshore (Box 33)
      - Social Security -- Continued benefits during appeal (Box 33)
      - Social Security financing, 3 folders (Box 33)
      - Senate Finance Committee hearings, 3 folders (Box 33)
      - Social Security Minimum Benefits amendment (Box 33)
      - Social Security Student Benefits Act (S.2107) (Box 33)
      - Soviet Union -- West European gas pipeline (Box 33)
      - Urban Mass Transportation Act amendment (S.2616)
        - The Budd Company, 3 folders (Box 33)
        - Handicapped transportation (Box 33)
      - Ukrainian Independence Day (Box 33)
    - 98th Congress, 1983-1984
      - Arabic community (Box 33)
      - Automobile trade (Box 33)
      - Biomedical Research Act (S.773), 2 folders
        - Fetal research (Box 33)
        - Heroin for terminally ill amendment (S.209) (Box 33)
      - Child Care Assistance Act (S.4) (Box 33)
      - Child Care Information and Referral Services Act (S.1360) (Box 34)
      - Civil Rights Act (S.2568) (Box 34)
      - Communications deregulation (Box 34)
      - Defense -- MX Missile (Box 34)
      - Economic Equity Act (Box 34)
      - Education for all handicapped children amendments (Box 34)
      - Education for Economic Security Act (S.1285) (Box 34)
      - Employee Retirement Income Security Act (Box 34)
      - Environmental Response Liability and Compensation Act -- Michigan sites, 3 folders (Box 34)
      - Environmental Response Compensation or Liability Act
        - 1984-1985 (Box 34)
        - National priorities list (Box 34)
      - Fair Labor Standards Act (S.213) (Box 34)
      - Fair Practices in Automotive Products Act (S.707)
        - 1984 (Box 34)
        - Briefing book (Box 34)
      - Family Violence Prevention and Services Act (S.1003)
        - 1983 (Box 34)
        - Infant Doe (Box 34)
      - Foreign affairs
        - Baltic States (Box 34)
        - Ireland (Box 34)
        - Lebanon (Box 34)
      - Handicapped Children’s Protection Act (S.2859)-Attorney’s fees (Box 34)
      - Health
        - Michigan, Owosso, Urban v. rural hospital status (Box 34)
        - Unemployed and unprotected study (Box 34)
      - Health Care for Unemployed Workers Act (S.1154), 2 folders (Box 34)
      - Employment Opportunities Act (S.242)
        - Hearings (Box 34)
        - Washington report on health legislation (Box 34)
      - Housing and community development legislation, 3 folders (Box 34)
      - Housing and community development legislation, 5 folders (Box 35)
      - Improved Standards for Laboratory Animals Act (S.657) (Box 35)
      - Industrial policy (Box 35)
      - Investment Corporation Act (Box 35)
      - Latchkey legislation, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Legal Services Corporation, 4 folders
        - Nominees (Box 35)
        - Reauthorization (Box 35)
      - Letters, Co-signed (Box 35)
      - Medicare Solvency and Health Care Financing Reform Act (S.2650) (Box 35)
      - Miscellaneous, 2 folders
        - Miscellaneous folder 1 (Box 35)
        - Miscellaneous folder 2 (Box 36)
      - Missing Children Assistance Act (S.2014) (Box 36)
      - National Investment Corporation Act, 2 folders (Box 36)
      - National Science Foundation amendment (Box 36)
      - National Taxpayers Legal Union Social Security proposal (Box 36)
      - Occupational therapy under Medicare (S.1615) (Box 36)
      - Older Americans Act amendments (S.2603) (Box 36)
      - Organ Transplant Act (S.2048), 2 folders (Box 36)
      - Outpatient eye surgery (Box 36)
      - Pictured Rocks National Lakeshore (S.620) (Box 36)
      - Religion in public schools (Box 36)
      - Rehabilitation Act amendments (S.1340)
        - Handicapped transportation (Box 36)
        - Reauthorization (Box 36)
      - Resource Conservation and Recovery Act (S.757) (Box 36)
      - Senate Children’s Caucus -- Gifted and Talented Children’s Enhancement Act (S.1975) (Box 36)
      - Sleeping Bear Dunes National Lakeshore (Box 36)
      - Benzie County (Box 36)
      - North Manitou Island (Box 36)
      - Small business briefing book, 2 folders (Box 36)
      - Social Security (Box 36)
      - Social Security Act amendments (S.1)
        - Amendments (Box 36)
        - Budget file (Box 36)
        - Floor materials (Box 36)
        - (S.1962) (Box 36)
      - Social Security disability legislation, 2 folders
        - SS legislation folder 1 (Box 36)
        - SS legislation folder 1 (Box 37)
      - Social Security reform (Box 37)
      - State Management and Technical Services Act
        - Crockett correspondence (Box 37)
        - Pennsylvania Technical Assistance Program (Box 37)
      - Unemployment insurance
        - 1983-1984 (Box 37)
        - Briefing book (Box 37)
      - Unemployment Insurance Law Reorganization Act -- alternatives (Box 37)
      - United States Academy of Peace Act (S.594) (Box 37)
      - Wilderness -- Miscellaneous (Box 37)
      - Women (Box 37)
      - World Health Day (S.J.Res.34) (Box 37)
    - 99th Congress, 1985-1986
      - Abortion
        - 1985-1986 (Box 37)
        - Briefing book (Box 37)
      - Access to Health Care Act (S.2402 S.2403) (Box 37)
      - Access to Health Care Act (S.2403) -- Hearings (Box 37)
      - Acquired Immunodeficiency Syndrome (Box 37)
      - Agriculture (Box 37)
      - Aid to Families with Dependent Children -- Error rate issue (Box 37)
      - Age Discrimination Act (S.1054) (Box 37)
      - Alcohol and advertising (Box 37)
      - Alternatives to Hospitalization for Medical Technology, Dependent Children Act (S.1793) (Box 37)
      - Animal Rights Bill (S.1233) -- amendments (Box 37)
      - Animal welfare (Box 37)
      - Antiviolence amendment to Hobbs Act (S.1774) (Box 37)
      - Automobile trade (Box 37)
      - Bills and resolutions co-sponsored (Box 37)
      - Center for Injury Control (Box 37)
      - Certified registered nurse anesthetists (Box 37)
      - Children’s Trust Fund Challenge Grant Act (Box 37)
      - Clean Water Act (S.1128)
        - 1986 (Box 37)
        - Conference issues (Box 37)
      - Clean Water Act amendment (S.765) (Box 37)
      - Community and Family Living Amendments (S.873) (Box 37)
      - Community schools program (Box 37)
      - Compassionate Pain Relief Act (S.70) (Box 37)
      - Constituents’ request for Drug Enforcement Administration interpretation (Box 38)
      - Correspondence -- Trade letters, 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Davis-Bacon Act (Box 38)
      - Defense
        - MX Missile (Box 38)
        - Nuclear weapons proliferation (Box 38)
        - Prisoners of War/Missing in Action (Box 38)
        - Spending (Box 38)
      - Department of Defense Reorganization Act (S.2295) (Box 38)
      - Department of Health and Human Resources -- Bowen nomination (Box 38)
      - Department of International Trade and Industry Act (S.923) (Box 38)
      - Dependent care grants, 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Diethylstilbestrol (Box 38)
      - Drug trafficking and crime legislation (Box 38)
      - Education -- Miscellaneous (Box 38)
      - Environment issues (Box 38)
      - Environmental legislation -- Michigan, 3 folders (Box 38)
      - Environmental Response compensation and Liability Act
        - Butterworth landfill (Box 38)
        - Charlevoix (Box 38)
        - Food exclusion (Box 38)
      - Federal Drug Administration user fees (Box 38)
      - Federal Unemployment Tax Act (Box 38)
      - Foreign affairs
        - Africa (Box 38)
        - Captive Nations Week (Box 38)
        - Genocide treaty (Box 38)
        - India (Box 38)
        - Ireland (Box 38)
        - Japanese trade (Box 38)
        - Jordan (Box 38)
        - Libya (Box 38)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 38)
        - Morocco (Box 38)
        - Nicaragua (Box 38)
        - Philippines (Box 38)
        - Poland (Box 38)
        - Russia (Box 38)
        - Soviet Union --
          - Divided-spouse cases resolved (Box 38)
          - Medvid case (Box 39)
          - Missing Americans (Box 39)
        - Terrorists (Box 39)
        - Yugoslavia (Box 39)
      - Foreign policy issues (Box 39)
      - Future Teacher Training Corps Act (Box 39)
      - Health -- Vaccine and product liability (Box 39)
      - Health Care for the Uninsured Act (Box 39)
      - Health insurance (Box 39)
      - Health Profession Student Loan Program (Box 39)
      - High Risk Occupational Disease Notification and Prevention Act (S.2050) (Box 39)
      - Health -- Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 39)
      - Higher Education Act reauthorization (Box 39)
      - Hill-Burton Act (Box 39)
      - Hobbs Act, 3 folders (Box 39)
      - Hungarian Freedom Fighters Day (S.J.Res.385) (Box 39)
      - Immigration
        - Legislation (Box 39)
        - Poland -- Refugees (Box 39)
      - Immigration Reform and Control Act
        - 1985 (Box 39)
        - Soviet Refugees, 1986 (Box 39)
      - Industrial competitiveness, 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Investment Corporation Act (Box 39)
      - Investment Finance Association Act (Box 39)
      - Infant mortality (Box 39)
      - Insurance for the unemployed -- Disproportionate share hospital (Box 39)
      - Latchkey legislation, 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Latvia (Box 40)
      - Letters co-signed, 3 folders (Box 40)
      - Lupus (Box 40)
      - Manufacturing clause of the Copyright Act (S.1822) (Box 40)
      - Medicaid for low income pregnant women (S.7) (Box 40)
      - Medicaid waivers
        - 1985 (Box 40)
        - Capitated ambulatory plan, 1985 (Box 40)
      - Medicare
        - Diagnostic related groups, 3 folders (Box 40)
        - Home health care (Box 40)
        - Medical education (Box 40)
        - Secondary payer (S.1604) (Box 40)
        - Medicare Quality Protection Act (S.2331) (Box 40)
        - Metropolitan statistical area hospitals (Box 40)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 40)
        - National Technology Foundation Act (S.1727) (Box 40)
        - Performing Arts Labor Relations amendment (S.670) (Box 40)
        - Pictured Rocks National Lakeshore (S.620) (Box 40)
        - Public investment data summaries (Box 40)
        - Prospective payment system (Box 40)
        - Protection and Advocacy for Mentally Ill Persons Act (S.974) (Box 40)
        - Religion in public schools (Box 40)
        - Research for Competitiveness Act (Box 40)
        - Resource Conservation and Recovery Act (S.757) (Box 40)
      - Senate Children’s Caucus, 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Senate Democratic Working Group on Economic Competitiveness (Box 41)
      - Senior Power Day (Box 41)
      - Service Contract Act (S.2638) (Box 41)
      - Sleeping Bear National Lakeshore
        - 1986Benzie County, 1985-1986 (Box 41)
      - Small Business Administration (Box 41)
      - Social Security
        - Disability advisory council (Box 41)
        - Disability legislation (Box 41)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 41)
        - State and local employees (Box 41)
        - Cost of living adjustment
          - Amendments (Box 41)
          - Background (Box 41)
          - Michigan (Box 41)
          - Roosevelt (Box 41)
      - Trust funds (Box 41)
      - South Africa
        - Anti-apartheid act (Box 41)
        - Anti-apartheid legislation, 2 folders (Box 41)
        - General statements supporting sanctions (Box 41)
      - Soviet Union, Jewry
        - Gubin case (Box 41)
        - Levin case (Box 41)
      - Special order on the failure of Senate action (Box 41)
      - Tax reform
        - Tax Reform Act, 2 folders (Box 41)
        - Individual retirement accounts (Box 42)
        - Michigan impact (Box 42)
        - Senate bill (Box 42)
      - Technology
        - Miscellaneous (Box 42)
        - Rosenstein, 2 folders (Box 42)
        - Windham, Pat (Box 42)
      - Trade
        - Briefing book (Box 42)
        - Competitiveness (Box 42)
        - Miscellaneous, 4 folders (Box 42)
        - Textiles (Box 42)
        - Workers’ rights (Box 42)
      - Ukrainian Independence Day (Box 42)
      - Unauthorized Drug Export Bill (Box 42)
      - Unemployment insurance (Box 42)
      - United States
        - Academy of Peace Act amendments (Box 42)
        - Data Bank Act (S.1829) (Box 42)
      - Universal Child Immunization Act (S.1917) (Box 42)
      - Urban development grant program, 2 folders (Box 42)
      - Veterans-POW/MIA-Recovery (Box 42)
      - Vietnam Veterans of America federal charter legislation (Box 42)
      - Widows’ disability bill (Box 42)
      - Women (Box 42)
      - Women’s economic equality act (Box 42)
      - Women’s equity package (Box 42)
      - Work opportunities retraining compact (S.2513) (Box 42)
      - World Food Day (Box 42)
      - World Health Day and World Health Week (Box 42)
    - 100th Congress, 1987-1988
      - Administrative
        - Legislative record (Box 42)
        - Voting record on auto issues (Box 42)
      - Agriculture-Drought relief bill (Box 43)
      - Alternative minimum tax (Box 43)
      - Bentsen trade legislation (Box 43)
      - Bill summaries (Box 43)
      - Bristol-Myers trade act (Box 43)
      - Charter bus service (Box 43)
      - Child care
        - ABC bill (S.1885) (Box 43)
        - Issues (Box 43)
        - In public housing (Box 43)
        - Partnership act (S.1071) (Box 43)
      - Child support enforcement, Access act
        - Children (Box 43)
        - Disabled-School bus safety (Box 43)
        - Economic equity tax act (Box 43)
        - Issues (Box 43)
      - Coast Guard budget cuts (Box 43)
      - Competitiveness (Box 43)
      - Correspondence (Box 43)
      - Defense
        - Agent Orange, 2 folders (Box 43)
        - Budget (Box 43)
      - Department of Defense authorization bill-Senate amendments
        - Intermediate-range nuclear forces treaty (Box 43)
        - Michigan
          - Allen Park Veterans Administration facility (Box 43)
          - Defense contracts (Box 43)
          - General (Box 43)
          - NWL Control Systems (Box 43)
          - Sales to Israel (Box 43)
          - Spending (Box 43)
          - University of Michigan -- Department of Defense bill (Box 43)
        - Palestinians-West Bank/Gaza Strip conflict (Box 43)
        - Spending (Box 43)
        - U.S./U.S.S.R. forces comparison (Box 43)
        - Weapons systems-Riegle pro/con (Box 43)
      - Dependent care (Box 43)
      - Diesel fuel tax (S.2075) (Box 43)
      - Disabled children’s access to supplemental security income and Medicaid benefits (Box 43)
      - Economic Equity Act (Box 43)
      - Education
        - Issue letters (Box 43)
        - Michigan-Michigan Education Association (Box 43)
        - Savings act (Box 43)
      - Employee leasing (Box 43)
      - Energy
        - Clean Water Act (Box 43)
        - Clean water bill (Box 43)
        - Ethanol blended fuels (Box 43)
        - Low-Income Home Energy Assistance Program
          - 1987 (Box 43)
          - 1988 (Box 43)
      - English Proficiency Act (S.629) (Box 43)
      - Environment (Box 43)
      - Endangered Species Act (S.675)
        - Ground water legislation (Box 43)
        - Michigan (Box 43)
        - Flood protection (Box 43)
        - Great Lakes
          - History (Box 43)
          - Research Lab (Box 43)
          - Water diversion
            - 1988 (Box 43)
            - News releases, 1988 (Box 43)
        - Rouge River -- Environmental Protection Agency (Box 43)
        - Sleeping Bear Dunes
          - Advisory commission (Box 43)
          - Appropriations (Box 43)
        - Solid waste dumping (Box 43)
        - Super fund, Right to know (Box 43)
      - Family Support Act-Corrections (Box 43)
      - Federal Unemployment Tax Act (Box 43)
      - Finance Committee hearing (Box 43)
      - Free trade agreement (Box 44)
      - General issues (Box 44)
      - General trade info (Box 44)
      - GMI-Mott tax issue-Tax-exempt organizations (Box 44)
      - Health
        - AIDS (S.1220) (Box 44)
        - Blue Cross and Medicare contract (Box 44)
        - Catastrophic, Final (Box 44)
        - Clinical labs (Box 44)
        - Commission for the prevention of infant mortality (Box 44)
        - Health Care for the Uninsured (S.177) (Box 44)
        - Match bill (S.2425) (Box 44)
        - Maintenance of effort amendment (Box 44)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 44)
        - Medicare
          - Medical education (Box 44)
          - Tech amendment, Lugar/Riegle (Box 44)
        - Old briefings (Box 44)
        - Personal care services (Box 44)
        - Rural hospitals (Box 44)
        - Share of lost Medicaid (Box 44)
        - Skilled nursing facilities (Box 44)
        - Uninsured
          - Mitchell/Riegle (Box 44)
          - Democratic Policy Committee hearing (Box 44)
      - Hearing on budget-Miller (Box 44)
      - Hearings-Self-injured workers compensation funds (Box 44)
      - High-Risk Occupational Disease Notification Act (S.79), 2 folders (Box 44)
      - Immigration-Kranich family case (Box 44)
      - Job Training Partnership Act (Box 44)
      - KLM flight 007 (Box 44)
      - Labor
        - Extended benefits penalty (Box 44)
        - General Motors-Trade act assistance (Box 44)
        - Grocer’s issues (Box 44)
        - Michigan-Unemployment, unemployment insurance (Box 44)
        - National Apprenticeship Act (S.901) (Box 44)
        - Workers’ rights, 3 folders
          - Workers Rights folders 1-2 (Box 44)
          - Workers Rights folder-3 (Box 45)
        - Latchkey (Box 45)
        - Legislative summary
          - 1987, 2 folders (Box 45)
          - 1988 (Box 45)
          - Energy (Box 45)
          - Environment, 3 folders (Box 45)
      - Letters initiated and co-signed by Riegle (Box 45)
      - Lithuanian Catholic religious liberty group-Membership letter (Box 45)
      - Low-income housing tax credit (Box 45)
      - Medicare-Rural services transitions act (S.1207) (Box 45)
      - Michigan
        - Harbor repair projects (Box 45)
        - Historic parks nomination (Box 45)
        - PBB disaster-Loan forgiveness (Box 45)
        - Regional office annual reports, 3 folders (Box 45)
      - Michigan Block Grant bill (S.2792) (Box 45)
      - Michigan Education Trust
        - 1987-1988 (Box 45)
        - Guaranteed tuition (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 45)
      - Missed votes (Box 45)
      - Mortgage revenue bonds (S.1522) (Box 45)
      - National Community Education Day (Box 45)
      - National Diethylstilbestrol Awareness Week (S.J.R. 17) (Box 45)
      - National Institute of Health, Silver Spring monkeys (Box 45)
      - National voluntary reunion registry (Box 45)
      - Omnibus Budget Reconciliation Act of (S.125)-Cafeteria plans, 1987 (Box 45)
      - Passive foreign investment company-Technical corrections (S.1296) (Box 45)
      - Pension
        - Finance Committee proposal (Box 45)
        - Football coaches (Box 45)
        - Motor Vehicle Manufacturers Association input (Box 46)
        - Summaries-Budget (Box 46)
      - Price/Anderson Act amendments (H.R.1414) (Box 46)
      - Research and development tax credit (Box 46)
      - Riegle statements (Box 46)
      - Riegle trade bill amendments (Box 46)
      - Romania-Human rights (Box 46)
      - Savings and loan/net operating losses (Box 46)
      - School bus safety, Handicapped transportation (Box 46)
      - Self-insured workers compensation funds tax-exempt status clarification act (Box 46)
      - Senior issues (Box 46)
      - Small business retirement (S.1426) (Box 46)
      - Social Security
        - Attorneys’ fees (Box 46)
        - Disability insurance program (Box 46)
        - Substantial gainful activity (Box 46)
        - Work incentives act (Box 46)
      - South Africa
        - Anti-Apartheid Act amendments of, 1988 (Box 46)
        - Anti-apartheid statements (Box 46)
        - Uranium ban (PL 99-440) (Box 46)
      - Soviet Union
        - Environment (Box 46)
        - Glasnost (Box 46)
        - Jewry, Braun case (Box 46)
      - Steel retirement (Box 46)
      - Student exclusion from Social Security taxes (Box 46)
      - Substantial gainful activity level (Box 46)
      - Targeted jobs tax credit (Box 46)
      - Tax
        - Employee educational assistance act (S.39) (Box 46)
        - Foster care bill (Box 46)
        - Gas guzzler excise (Box 46)
        - Interest allocation rules (Box 46)
        - Overhaul package (S.670) (Box 46)
        - Pension reform, General (Box 46)
        - Publishers R and D expenses (Box 46)
        - Utility over-collections (Box 46)
        - World Peace Tax Fund (Box 46)
      - Tax education issues (Box 46)
      - Tax notes (Box 46)
      - Tax Reform Act-Nondiscrimination rules (S.89) (Box 46)
      - Tax Reform Act of Rogers tax problem (S.502), 1986 (Box 46)
      - Taxation of foreign insurance companies-Amendments (S.842) (Box 46)
      - Taxes
        - 1988 (Box 46)
        - Riegle legislative activity on taxes, 1987 (Box 46)
        - Technical corrections
          - Amendments (Box 46)
          - Tax treaty (Box 46)
      - Telecommunications act (Box 46)
      - Textile and Apparel Trade Act (S.2662 S.549) (Box 46)
      - Textiles (Box 46)
      - Title IV-E, Foster-care amendments (Box 46)
      - Title XX-Tribal set-aside (Box 46)
      - Trade
        - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)-Super 301
          - Korea (Box 47)
          - Michigan (Box 47)
          - Semi-conductors, 4 folders (Box 47)